School of the Museum of Fine Arts Records UA133
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Audiovisual materials, 1980 -- 2016; UA133.011; 14.4 Linear Feet
  - Nayland Blake, 1998-11-05; UA133.011.081.00024 (Box 81)
  - Visiting Artists Lecture - Glass Lecture, 1998-10-30; UA133.011.081.00025 (Box 81)
    Nicolas, Sylvia
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1998-10-27; UA133.011.081.00026 (Box 81)
    Steinbeck, Haim
  - Yvonne Rainer, 1997-09-18; UA133.011.081.00027 (Box 81)
    Rainer, Yvonne
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1996-09-06; UA133.011.081.00028 (Box 81)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1997-02-20; UA133.011.081.00029 (Box 81)
    Van Zijst, Jan Willem; Van der Burgatt, Angela
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1998-10-23; UA133.011.081.00030 (Box 81)
  - Arthur C. Danto, 1998-10-20; UA133.011.081.00031 (Box 81)
  - Marcia Tucker, 1998-10-14; UA133.011.081.00032 (Box 81)
    Tucker, Marcia
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1998-10-09; UA133.011.081.00033 (Box 81)
    Mayerson, Keith
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1997-02-18; UA133.011.081.00034 (Box 81)
    Tierny, Hanne
  - Beckwith Lecture, 1998-10-05; UA133.011.081.00035 (Box 81)
    Graham, Dan
  - Gallery Panel Discussion, 1998-09-21; UA133.011.081.00036 (Box 81)
    Basilico, Stephano; Inglett, Susan; Sullivan, David
  - Barbara Hammer, 1997-01-01; UA133.011.081.00037 (Box 81)
    Hammer, Barbara
  - Lynda Benglis, 1997-01-01; UA133.011.081.00038 (Box 81)
    Benglis, Lynda
  - Jhon Katz, 1997-03-03; UA133.011.081.00039 (Box 81)
    Katz, Jhon
  - Regina Frank, 1998-10-01; UA133.011.081.00040 (Box 81)
    Frank, Regina
  - Dan Graham, circa 1998; UA133.011.081.00041 (Box 81)
  - Dan Graham Beckwith Lecture, 1998-10-05; UA133.011.081.00042 (Box 81)
  - Bill Viola Beckwith Lecture, 1996-11-02; UA133.011.081.00043 (Box 81)
  - Bob Flanagan Panel discussion, 1995-02-09; UA133.011.081.00044 (Box 81)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1997-03-03; UA133.011.081.00045 (Box 81)
    Winters, Sandy
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1997-01-24; UA133.011.081.00046 (Box 81)
    Schuyff, Peter
  - Terry Adkins, 1997-10-23; UA133.011.081.00047 (Box 81)
    Adkins, Terry
  - Mira Schor, 1997-10-17; UA133.011.081.00048 (Box 81)
    Schor, Mira
  - Jerry Saltz, 1997-10-09; UA133.011.081.00049 (Box 81)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1995-02-03; UA133.011.081.00050 (Box 81)
    Mueller, Stephan
  - John Lees, 1995-02-07; UA133.011.081.00051 (Box 81)
    Lees, John
  - Ronald Jones, 1995-11-09; UA133.011.081.00052 (Box 81)
    Jones, Ronald
  - Jerry Saltz, 1997-10-01; UA133.011.081.00053 (Box 81)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Crisus, 1994-02-24; UA133.011.082.00001 (Box 82)
    Becker, Jeff; McClay, Malcolm
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Crisus (Copy), 1994-02-24; UA133.011.082.00002 (Box 82)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1994-02-25; UA133.011.082.00003 (Box 82)
    Porter, Katherine
  - Gallery Talk, 1993-03-03; UA133.011.082.00004 (Box 82)
    Granet, Ilona
  - Printmaker, Sculptor, Painter - Beckwith Lecture, 1992-10-11; UA133.011.082.00005 (Box 82)
    Frank, Mary
  - Beckwith Lecture, 1993-10-04; UA133.011.082.00006 (Box 82)
    Finley, Karen
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - TechnoFrolic's Founder and Director, 1993-07-01; UA133.011.082.00007 (Box 82)
    Durlach, David
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1994-01-20; UA133.011.082.00008 (Box 82)
    Ziegler, Mel; Ericson, Kate
  - Beckwith Lecture (Tape 1), 1995-11-02; UA133.011.082.00009 (Box 82)
  - Tom Freedman, 1998-01-28; UA133.011.082.00010 (Box 82)
    Freedman, Tom
  - Roni Horn, 1996-10-21; UA133.011.082.00011 (Box 82)
    Horn, Roni
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1996-01-19; UA133.011.082.00012 (Box 82)
    Zakanitch, Robert
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1996-01-19; UA133.011.082.00013 (Box 82)
  - Wait for Sound, 1992-02-27; UA133.011.082.00014 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1992-11-04; UA133.011.082.00015 (Box 82)
    Rath, Alan
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1994-01-20; UA133.011.082.00016 (Box 82)
  - Invitational, 1993-03-09; UA133.011.082.00017 (Box 82)
    Min, Yong Soon
  - Judie Bamber, 1996-01-01; UA133.011.082.00018 (Box 82)
  - Ron Jones, 1997-11-04; UA133.011.082.00019 (Box 82)
    Jones, Ron
  - Laurie Linquist, 1998-02-26; UA133.011.082.00020 (Box 82)
    Linquist, Laurie
  - MFA School AIDS Day (various years), 1992-09-04; UA133.011.082.00021 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist lecture: group material, 1993-10-25; UA133.011.082.00022 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1996-10-22; UA133.011.082.00023 (Box 82)
    Grenman, Simon; Sperandio, Christopher
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1996-01-25; UA133.011.082.00024 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1996-08-07; UA133.011.082.00025 (Box 82)
    Moonelis, Judy
  - Jerry Saltz, 1997-10-30; UA133.011.082.00026 (Box 82)
  - Gallery Talk, 1997-10-30, 1997-11-04; UA133.011.082.00027 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 1997-10-27; UA133.011.082.00028 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1994-09-22; UA133.011.082.00029 (Box 82)
    Avery, Eric
  - Printmaker, Sculptor, Painter - Beckwith Lecture, 1992-11-10; UA133.011.082.00030 (Box 82)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series - Copy, 1993-11-05; UA133.011.082.00031 (Box 82)
    Kass, Deborah
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1994-02-17; UA133.011.082.00032 (Box 82)
    Dopitova, Milena
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1992-10-29; UA133.011.082.00033 (Box 82)
  - Lecture and mobile exhibition, 1992-10-15; UA133.011.082.00034 (Box 82)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1993-03-04; UA133.011.082.00035 (Box 82)
    Cross, Dorothy
  - Lardiner Exhibit, 1992-09-16; UA133.011.082.00036 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1992-10-01; UA133.011.082.00037 (Box 82)
    Kindness, John
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1993-11-05; UA133.011.082.00038 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Copy, 1994-02-01; UA133.011.082.00039 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1994-02-10; UA133.011.082.00040 (Box 82)
  - Lardiner Exhibit, 1992-09-16; UA133.011.082.00041 (Box 82)
  - Medici Presentation, 1993-03-03; UA133.011.082.00042 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Critic, 1993-02-01; UA133.011.082.00043 (Box 82)
  - Invitational, 1993-03-09; UA133.011.082.00044 (Box 82)
  - Tommy Simpson, 1994-01-28; UA133.011.082.00045 (Box 82)
    Simpson, Tommy
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1992-10-21; UA133.011.082.00046 (Box 82)
    Menard, Lloyd
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1993-09-09; UA133.011.082.00047 (Box 82)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1991-10-31; UA133.011.082.00048 (Box 82)
    Maruyama, Wendy
  - Visiting Artist Lecture - Stop the Church, 1991-11-14; UA133.011.082.00049 (Box 82)
    Hilferty, Robert
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1992-04-25; UA133.011.082.00050 (Box 82)
    Amenoff, Gregory
  - Race in Media" Symposium, 1998-01-01; UA133.011.082.00051 (Box 82)
  - Eurasienstab, 1968-01-01; UA133.011.083.00001 (Box 83)
    Beauys, Joseph
  - Graduate Colloquium - (Tape 1), 2004-02-25; UA133.011.083.00002 (Box 83)
    Galluci, Barbara; Bennet, Mark; Ferrara, Annette; Kich, Daniel; Coffee, Kiera
  - Camp Brookwood, 1975-06-01; UA133.011.083.00003 (Box 83)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2005-09-14; UA133.011.083.00004 (Box 83)
    Robinson, Nadine
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2006-10-10; UA133.011.083.00005 (Box 83)
    Cooke, Lynne
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2005-09-14; UA133.011.083.00006 (Box 83)
    Freeman, Nan
  - 12:30 Lecture, 2004-02-15; UA133.011.083.00007 (Box 83)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2004-02-17; UA133.011.083.00008 (Box 83)
    Bove, Carol
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2005-02-15; UA133.011.083.00009 (Box 83)
    Gatson, Rico
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2003-10-28; UA133.011.083.00010 (Box 83)
    Feher, Tony
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2004-02-25; UA133.011.083.00011 (Box 83)
    Davie, Karin
  - Graduate Colloquium - (Tape 2), 2004-02-25; UA133.011.083.00012 (Box 83)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2004-10-19; UA133.011.083.00013 (Box 83)
    Chu, Anne
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture, 2005-02-22; UA133.011.083.00014 (Box 83)
    Hanson, Chris; Sonnenberg, Hendrika
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2003-10-27; UA133.011.083.00015 (Box 83)
    Foster, Hal
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2003-10-27; UA133.011.083.00016 (Box 83)
    Parker, Erik
  - Fifty Years of Painting w/ Dr. Tritobia Benjamin, 2006-09-27; UA133.011.083.00017 (Box 83)
    Jones, Lois Mailou
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2006-09-26; UA133.011.083.00018 (Box 83)
    Davis, Taylor
  - Critic, 2003-10-09; UA133.011.083.00019 (Box 83)
    Goldberg, Vicki
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2004-03-02; UA133.011.083.00020 (Box 83)
    Knight, Ross
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2003-09-16; UA133.011.083.00021 (Box 83)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2003-09-15; UA133.011.083.00022 (Box 83)
    Pomara, Jon
  - Printmaking, 2003-04-02; UA133.011.083.00023 (Box 83)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2003-04-01; UA133.011.083.00024 (Box 83)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2003-01-21; UA133.011.083.00025 (Box 83)
    McCoy, Jennifer; McCoy, Kevin
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2003-01-23; UA133.011.083.00026 (Box 83)
    Williams, Carla
  - Young Photography: Panel Discussion, 2003-01-23; UA133.011.083.00027 (Box 83)
  - Photography Lecture, 2003-09-23; UA133.011.083.00028 (Box 83)
    Samaras, Connie
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2003-09-23; UA133.011.083.00029 (Box 83)
    Heyl, Charline von
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2003-09-30; UA133.011.083.00030 (Box 83)
    Serge, Michelle
  - Critic, 2003-10-06; UA133.011.083.00031 (Box 83)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2004-11-01; UA133.011.083.00032 (Box 83)
    Whitney, Stanley
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2004-11-02; UA133.011.083.00033 (Box 83)
    Mingwei, Lee
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-03-06; UA133.011.083.00034 (Box 83)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-03-12; UA133.011.083.00035 (Box 83)
  - Eight Painters Lecture Series, 2007-04-10; UA133.011.083.00036 (Box 83)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-04-10; UA133.011.083.00037 (Box 83)
  - Eight Painters Lecture Series, 2007-09-11; UA133.011.083.00038 (Box 83)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2006-10-24; UA133.011.083.00039 (Box 83)
    Rottenberg, Mika
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-02-06; UA133.011.083.00040 (Box 83)
  - Eight Painters Lecture, 2007-02-13; UA133.011.083.00041 (Box 83)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-03-02; UA133.011.083.00042 (Box 83)
  - Fabric Workshop, 2006-10-03; UA133.011.083.00043 (Box 83)
    Friel, Mary Anne
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-10-14; UA133.011.084.00001 (Box 84)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-10-14; UA133.011.084.00002 (Box 84)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-10-07; UA133.011.084.00003 (Box 84)
    Marston, Heidi M.
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-10-13; UA133.011.084.00004 (Box 84)
    McMurry, Jamie
  - Unmasking Shadow, 2004-10-13; UA133.011.084.00005 (Box 84)
    Dulloo, Djuneid
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2004-10-04; UA133.011.084.00006 (Box 84)
    Enwezor, Okwui
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2004-10-05; UA133.011.084.00007 (Box 84)
    Kalpakjian, Craig
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1991-10-24; UA133.011.084.00008 (Box 84)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2006-09-12; UA133.011.084.00009 (Box 84)
  - Chaos and Psyche, 1991-01-01; UA133.011.084.00010 (Box 84)
    Koufopoulou, Lila
  - Cameron Shaw, 1991-09-19; UA133.011.084.00011 (Box 84)
    Shaw, Cameron
  - Dave Cole lecture, 2006-09-09; UA133.011.084.00012 (Box 84)
    Cole, Dave
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1992-09-25; UA133.011.084.00013 (Box 84)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1993-10-08; UA133.011.084.00014 (Box 84)
    Palazzolo, Carl
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1993-10-21; UA133.011.084.00015 (Box 84)
    Phillips, David
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series - copy, 1993-10-21; UA133.011.084.00016 (Box 84)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1994-09-29; UA133.011.084.00017 (Box 84)
    Levine, Erik
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1993-10-08; UA133.011.084.00018 (Box 84)
  - Beckwith Lecture, 1993-10-04; UA133.011.084.00019 (Box 84)
  - New Territory: Art from East Germany, 1990-10-31; UA133.011.084.00020 (Box 84)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1988-03-06; UA133.011.084.00021 (Box 84)
  - The Int. Man and Int. Woman in the Creative Activity - Workshop, 1988-03-05; UA133.011.084.00022 (Box 84)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-09-27; UA133.011.084.00023 (Box 84)
    Ksiazek, Wlodzimierz
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-09-27; UA133.011.084.00024 (Box 84)
    Massumi, Brian
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2005-10-03; UA133.011.084.00025 (Box 84)
    Doud, Tim
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2005-10-04; UA133.011.084.00026 (Box 84)
    McGinness, Ryan
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2005-10-05; UA133.011.084.00027 (Box 84)
    Finch, Spencer
  - The Body of the Text, 2004-03-03; UA133.011.084.00028 (Box 84)
    Neuenschwander, Brody
  - Rock My Religion, 1982-01-01; UA133.011.084.00029 (Box 84)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2004-03-16; UA133.011.084.00030 (Box 84)
    Phelan, Michael
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2004-09-21; UA133.011.084.00031 (Box 84)
    Swartz, Julianne
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-09-22; UA133.011.084.00032 (Box 84)
    Feingold, Ken
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2004-09-23; UA133.011.084.00033 (Box 84)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2004-09-27; UA133.011.084.00034 (Box 84)
    Dubnau, Jenny
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2002-11-04; UA133.011.084.00035 (Box 84)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2003-01-21; UA133.011.084.00036 (Box 84)
  - Tongues Untied, 1989-01-01; UA133.011.084.00037 (Box 84)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2004-03-08; UA133.011.084.00038 (Box 84)
    Odita, Odili Donald
  - Dreams of Breathe / Don't Breathe Home, 1988-09-06; UA133.011.084.00039 (Box 84)
    Arsem, Marilyn
  - Performance, 1988-03-03; UA133.011.084.00040 (Box 84)
    Bernard, Karen
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1988-08-08; UA133.011.084.00041 (Box 84)
  - Performance, 1988-03-14; UA133.011.084.00042 (Box 84)
  - Performance Art Festival '89 Highlights, 1989-01-01; UA133.011.084.00043 (Box 84)
    Cleveland Public Theatre
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1992-01-23; UA133.011.084.00044 (Box 84)
  - Mary Ellen Carroll lecture, 2005-09-28; UA133.011.084.00045 (Box 84)
    Carroll, Mary Ellen
  - Linda Norden lecture, 2005-09-27; UA133.011.084.00046 (Box 84)
    Norden, Linda
  - Beckwith Lecture: W. J. T. Mitchell, 2005-09-19; UA133.011.084.00047 (Box 84)
    Mitchell, W. J. T.
  - Beckwith Lecture: W. J. T. Mitchell, 2005-09-19; UA133.011.084.00048 (Box 84)
  - Eight Painters Lecture, 2007-10-02; UA133.011.085.00001 (Box 85)
  - Eight Painters Lecture Series, 2007-10-16; UA133.011.085.00002 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-10-09; UA133.011.085.00003 (Box 85)
    Ford, Kinga
  - Eight Painters Lecture Series, 2007-04-10; UA133.011.085.00004 (Box 85)
  - Eight Painters Lecture Series, 2007-04-10; UA133.011.085.00005 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-09-26; UA133.011.085.00006 (Box 85)
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2007-10-03; UA133.011.085.00007 (Box 85)
    Dalrymple Henderson, Linda
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-10-10; UA133.011.085.00008 (Box 85)
    Noit, Banai
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-01-26; UA133.011.085.00009 (Box 85)
  - Annual - "Good", 2007-01-01; UA133.011.085.00010 (Box 85)
  - Orientation - Faculty/Student Presentations, 2007; UA133.011.085.00011 (Box 85)
    Images of student work.
  - Eight Painters Lecture Series, 2007-09-11; UA133.011.085.00012 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-03-13; UA133.011.085.00013 (Box 85)
  - Eight Painters Lecture, 2007-02-13; UA133.011.085.00014 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2007-03-02; UA133.011.085.00015 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-11-13; UA133.011.085.00016 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-02-06; UA133.011.085.00017 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-03-12; UA133.011.085.00018 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-03-12; UA133.011.085.00019 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptures Lecture Series, 2007-03-06; UA133.011.085.00020 (Box 85)
    Olivier, Karyn
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-10-23; UA133.011.085.00021 (Box 85)
  - Eight Photographers Lecture Series, 2007-09-20; UA133.011.085.00022 (Box 85)
  - Harvard Curator, 2007-10-02; UA133.011.085.00023 (Box 85)
    Molesworth, Helen
  - Eighth Painters, 2007-03-27; UA133.011.085.00024 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2007-09-18; UA133.011.085.00025 (Box 85)
  - Diana Cooper, 2009-02-17; UA133.011.085.00026 (Box 85)
    Cooper, Diana, Lady, 1892-.
  - Moyra Davey, 2009-11-05; UA133.011.085.00027 (Box 85)
  - Moyra Davey, 2009-11-05; UA133.011.085.00028 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2009-11-17; UA133.011.085.00029 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2009-11-17; UA133.011.085.00030 (Box 85)
  - Chie Fueki, 2009-11-10; UA133.011.085.00031 (Box 85)
  - Lalla Essaydi, 2009-01-22; UA133.011.085.00032 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2009-02-10; UA133.011.085.00033 (Box 85)
  - Josephine Halvorson, 2009-09-29; UA133.011.085.00034 (Box 85)
  - Wendy Jacob, 2009-09-14; UA133.011.085.00035 (Box 85)
  - Brad Kahlhamer, 2009-02-24; UA133.011.085.00036 (Box 85)
  - Disc 1 of 2, 2009-03-31; UA133.011.085.00037 (Box 85)
  - Disc 2 of 2, 2009-03-31; UA133.011.085.00038 (Box 85)
  - Inka Essenhigh, 2008-11-25; UA133.011.085.00039 (Box 85)
  - MFA, Riley Auditorium, 2008-09-25; UA133.011.085.00040 (Box 85)
  - Chris Doyle, 2008-11-18; UA133.011.085.00041 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2008-02-28; UA133.011.085.00042 (Box 85)
    Flynn, William
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-01-29; UA133.011.085.00043 (Box 85)
  - Eight Photographers, 2008-11-13; UA133.011.085.00044 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-03-04; UA133.011.085.00045 (Box 85)
  - Hilary Harkness, 2008-10-14; UA133.011.085.00046 (Box 85)
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series, 2008-01-31; UA133.011.085.00047 (Box 85)
  - Cory Arcangel, 2008-02-13; UA133.011.085.00048 (Box 85)
    Arcangel, Cory
  - Beckwith Lecture - Unframing Experience, 2008-09-16; UA133.011.085.00049 (Box 85)
    Baas, Jacquelynn
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2007-10-30; UA133.011.085.00050 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2005-11-02; UA133.011.085.00051 (Box 85)
  - Animation Lecture, 2008-03-05; UA133.011.085.00052 (Box 85)
  - Nina Katchadourian, 2008-04-08; UA133.011.085.00053 (Box 85)
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series, 2008-04-01; UA133.011.085.00054 (Box 85)
  - Michelle Lopez, 2008-10-21; UA133.011.085.00055 (Box 85)
  - Chris Martin, 2008-09-30; UA133.011.085.00056 (Box 85)
  - Esteban Pastorino, 2008-04-03; UA133.011.085.00057 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-01-30; UA133.011.085.00058 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2008-04-15; UA133.011.085.00059 (Box 85)
  - Four Photographers Lecture Series, 2008-03-13; UA133.011.085.00060 (Box 85)
    Sanguinetti, Alessandra
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2008-03-25; UA133.011.085.00061 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2008-03-25; UA133.011.085.00062 (Box 85)
  - Courtney Smith, 2008-11-04; UA133.011.085.00063 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2008-02-26; UA133.011.085.00064 (Box 85)
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2000-01-01; UA133.011.085.00065 (Box 85)
    Hickey, Dave
  - Beverly Semmes, 2009-10-27; UA133.011.085.00066 (Box 85)
  - Dana Schutz, 2009-04-09; UA133.011.085.00067 (Box 85)
  - Dana Schutz, 2009-04-09; UA133.011.085.00068 (Box 85)
  - Laurel Nakadate, 2009-11-18; UA133.011.085.00069 (Box 85)
  - Disc 2 of 2, 2009-03-31; UA133.011.085.00070 (Box 85)
  - Disc 1 of 2, 2009-03-31; UA133.011.085.00071 (Box 85)
  - Beverly Semmes, 2009-10-27; UA133.011.085.00072 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2003-09-30; UA133.011.085.00073 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2003-09-23; UA133.011.085.00074 (Box 85)
  - Critic, 2003-10-06; UA133.011.085.00075 (Box 85)
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2003-10-27; UA133.011.085.00076 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2003-09-16; UA133.011.085.00077 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1994-11-01; UA133.011.085.00078 (Box 85)
    Antoni, Janine
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1996-01-19; UA133.011.085.00079 (Box 85)
  - Light Dance - Performance Documentation, 1995; UA133.011.085.00080 (Box 85)
    Riskin, Seth
  - Big Bob Flanagan, 1995-01-01; UA133.011.085.00081 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 1995-01-11; UA133.011.085.00082 (Box 85)
    Plimack Mangold, Sylvia
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 1997-10-27; UA133.011.085.00083 (Box 85)
    Taaffe, Philip
  - Ron Jones, 1997-11-04; UA133.011.085.00084 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1997-09-26; UA133.011.085.00085 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 1999-11-04; UA133.011.085.00086 (Box 85)
  - Mary Ellen Strom, 1999-10-26; UA133.011.085.00087 (Box 85)
  - Marcia Tucker, 1998-10-14; UA133.011.085.00088 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 1999-05-10; UA133.011.085.00089 (Box 85)
  - Arthur C. Danto, 1998-10-20; UA133.011.085.00090 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 1999-10-25; UA133.011.085.00091 (Box 85)
  - Beckwith Lecture, 1999-10-20; UA133.011.085.00092 (Box 85)
  - Artist Lecture Series, 1999-12-10; UA133.011.085.00093 (Box 85)
  - Freida Lee Mock, 1999-09-21; UA133.011.085.00094 (Box 85)
    Mock, Freida Lee
  - Gallery Talk, 2001-12-10; UA133.011.085.00095 (Box 85)
  - Gallery Talk, 2001-01-11; UA133.011.085.00096 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2001-01-23; UA133.011.085.00097 (Box 85)
  - In Conversation, 2002-09-30; UA133.011.085.00098 (Box 85)
  - In Conversation, 2002-09-30; UA133.011.085.00099 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2002-12-02; UA133.011.085.00100 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2002-11-05; UA133.011.085.00101 (Box 85)
    Harrison, Rachel
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2002-01-23; UA133.011.085.00102 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series - Installation Artist, 2002-01-22; UA133.011.085.00103 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2002-09-30; UA133.011.085.00104 (Box 85)
  - Four Painters Lecture Series, 2002-09-30; UA133.011.085.00105 (Box 85)
  - Tim Doud, 2005-10-03; UA133.011.085.00106 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2005-10-05; UA133.011.085.00107 (Box 85)
  - Mary Ellen Carroll, 2005-09-28; UA133.011.085.00108 (Box 85)
  - Taryn Simon, 2009-02-12; UA133.011.085.00109 (Box 85)
  - Wheaton Lecture, 2006-09-13; UA133.011.085.00110 (Box 85)
    Evans, Tripp
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2006-10-03; UA133.011.085.00111 (Box 85)
  - Beckwith Lecture, 2006-10-04; UA133.011.085.00112 (Box 85)
  - Dave Cole, 2006-09-06; UA133.011.085.00113 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-01-25; UA133.011.085.00114 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2006-09-26; UA133.011.085.00115 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture Series, 2006-09-26; UA133.011.085.00116 (Box 85)
  - Mark Handforth, 2006-02-21; UA133.011.085.00117 (Box 85)
    Handforth, Mark
  - Sheila Pepe, 2006-09-19; UA133.011.085.00118 (Box 85)
    Pepe, Sheila
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2006-03-07; UA133.011.085.00119 (Box 85)
    Min, Yunhee
  - Crown Point Press Lectures, 2006-01-01; UA133.011.085.00120 (Box 85)
    Brown, Kathan; Marioni, Tom
  - Fifty Years of Painting w/ Dr. Tritobia Benjamin, 2006-09-27; UA133.011.085.00121 (Box 85)
  - Lecture by Edmund Barry Gaither, 2006-09-18; UA133.011.085.00122 (Box 85)
  - Fabric Workshop, 2006-10-03; UA133.011.085.00123 (Box 85)
  - Four Sculptors Lecture Series, 2006-10-24; UA133.011.085.00124 (Box 85)
  - Eight Sculptors Lecture Series, 2006-09-12; UA133.011.085.00125 (Box 85)
  - Visiting Artist Lecture, 2005-10-06; UA133.011.085.00126 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000; UA133.011.085.00127 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-04-14; UA133.011.085.00128 (Box 85)
  - Faculty Lecture Series, 2000-02-01; UA133.011.085.00129 (Box 85)
  - MFA Lecture, 2000-01-01; UA133.011.085.00130 (Box 85)
    Mikhailov, Boris